JP Freeley

Personal Information

In: http://linkedin.com/in/jpfreeley

Email: jpf321@gmail.com

git: http://jpfreeley.github.io

T: @JP_Freeley

Education

Immersive, Data ScienceDecember 2016General AssemblyNew York, NY

Masters, Computer Science June 1997 Pace University New York, NY

Bachelors, Wildlife BiologyCornell University
June 1993
Ithaca, NY

Experience

BlueBlastMedia March 2006 – Innovation Consultant Present

- Key manager for at least two projects annually with revenues of \$250,000 or more
- Maintained competitive advantage through seeking and delivering at least one new product offering a year
- Identified and deployed backend asset management system to streamline project work flow

Volunteer

Co-President
 PS101Q's Parents' Association Inc
 July 2015 – Present

Creator - Moderator
 Forest Hills Crime Watch
 August 2012 - Present

Community Liaison
 NYPD
 August 2015 – Present

• Creator - Moderator Various Active LinkedIn Groups

Key Skills

Knowledge of:

- Python
- PHP
- PERL
- Tableau
- AWS
- SQL (Postgres/mySQL)
- HTML/CSS
- LINUX
- ESRI Arc/Info

Key Competencies

- Data Science
- MarCom
- Social Media
- IoT
- EDA

Personal Skills

- Critical Thinking
- Creative Problem Solving
- Strategic Planning
- Analytics

Achievements

OAAA - Obie Award 2008

Hobbies & Interests

- Billiards
- Hiking
- Cycling
- Photography
- Family

References

References will be provided on request

Personal Statement

My experience helps me to understand. My tenacity helps me to achieve. My communication helps me to inform. Data drives the results. I am a very intelligent individual with the ability to adapt and learn in any situation. I have picked up many different skills over the years. I am comfortable being thrown into a situation and working through it to completion. I am very hands on and focused but also work well as a team member. I get enjoyment from attaining both personal and group goals and take the time to celebrate notable achievements.

Copyright information - Please read

© This <u>Free Resume Template</u> is the copyright of Hloom.com. You can download and modify this template for your own personal use to create a resume for yourself, or for someone else. You can (and should!) <u>remove this copyright notice</u> before sending your resume to potential employers.

You may not distribute or resell this template, or its derivatives, and you may not make it available on other websites without our prior permission. All sharing of this template must be done using a link to http://www.hloom.com/download-professional-resume-templates/. For any questions relating to the use of this template please email us - info@hloom.com